Guide to the Edward Lee Plumb Papers, 1856-1912
Department of Special Collections
- CLIPPINGS (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Miscellaneous memorabilla - menu printed on cloth with Plumb's name in paint., one item - (Box 8, Folder 102)
Marshall, M. B., 8, 9.
Martinez, Guillermo, 42.
Mata, J. M., 11, 20, 30, 36.
Maximilian (Ferdinand Maximilian Joseph, archduke of Austria & emperor of Mexico) mentioned in 6, 8, 9, 55 (Plumb's material on).
Mayoso, Martin, 11.
Mejia, Ignacio, 19, 21, 23, 34, 38 (mention).
Mexican Central Railroad, 44.
Mexican International Railroad, 45-47, 57, 62.
Mexican Pacific Coal and Iron Mining and Land Co., 1-4.
Mexican Southern Railroad, 47.
Mexico, Archbishop of, see Labastida.
Mexico - Commerce, 5, 6, 21, 35, 37, 40, 42, 62.
Mexico - Description and travel, 1-4.
Mexico - Finances and foreign debt, 2, 4-7, 11, 12, 31, 32, 33, 44, 46, 57, 62.
Mexico - History - Foreign invasion, 4, 6-9, 55 (Plumb's material on), 62.
Mexico - Mines and mining, 1-3, 33, 43, 44, 62.
Mexico - Politics and government, 2-12, 14, 19-24, 26, 28, 31, 33, 34, 36-38, 40, 41, 43, 44, 51, 57, 58, 62-65, 70-72, 76, 77, 85-101 and container vols. 9-12.
Mexico - Railroads, 1, 6, 14, 19-37, 40, 44-46, 57, 62, 63, 86-99.
Middleton, H. T. C., 10.
Mitchell, Addison, 55.
Morgan, John Tyler, 56.
Moses, Isaac, 8.
Navarro, Juan N., 45.
Nelson, Thomas H., 23, 24, 29, 37, 40, 43.
New Almaden Quicksilver Mine, 24. and vol. 2 of scrapbook (see its index)
Newbold, R. S., 9.
Newbold, William, 24, 29, 35, 36.
New Orleans, 12.
New Orleans - Vera Cruz steamers, 19, 36.
Nicaragua canal, 40, 45, 48, 52, 69.
Northern Pacific Railroad, 42, 44, 61, 82.
Nuestra Senora mine, 44.
Ocampo de Mata, Josefa, 26.
Ord, Edward O. C., 33 (mention), 34 (ltr. to), 38 (ltrs. to).
Pacific Railroad, 61, 81.
Paige, Nath., 43.
Palmer, Edward F., 9.
Palmer, William Jackson, 21, 24, 45.
Panama canal, 56, 57, 74.
Paris (France) Exposition, 41.
Pearsall, Thomas M., 27, 45, 46.
Pelleschi, Giovanni, 53.
Phelps, William Walter, 30, 31, 35.
Phillipines, 55, 56.
Pierce, Thomas W., 32, 36, 38 (copy).
Plumb, Albert Hale, 12, 32, 43.
Poe, Orlando Metcalfe, 43.
Poole, Henry Ward, 2, 3.
Poor, Charles H., 16.
Poore, Benjamin Perley, 35.
Porter, Horace, 16.
Poston, Charles Debrille, 9, 19, 28, 34.
Pothonier, Charles Sligo de, 29, 34, 35, 39, 40.
Puerto Rico, 54.
Queretaro, siege of, 1867, 8, 9.
Railroads, 1, 2, 10, 19-37, 39-47, 57, 59, 60, 61, 62, 78-99.
Ramiro, Luis, 27, 36.
Raphel, Joseph A., 13.
Reed, Samuel C., 22.
Richardson, D. S., 31, 32.
Riley, Henry Chauncey, 21.
Roberts, Dionisio Lopez, 14, 19.
Roberts, William Milnor, 32, 33, 35, 36.
Roelofson, William F., 19.
Romero, José M., 27, 30.
Romero, Matías, 4, 5, 7-14, 16, 19-22, 31, 48, 51-54.
Romero Rubio, Manuel, 37.
Rosecrans, William Starke, 12, 64, 78.
Ruthven, G. R., 10, 15.
Salm-Salm, Felix Nepomuk, Prince, mentioned, 10.
Santacilia y Palacios, Pedro, 9, 20, 25,
Saulnier, E. H., 8, 10.
Savage, Thomas S., 10.
Schleicher Gustave, 42, 43 (mention).
Scott, Thomas A., 31, 41.
Sagura, Luis G. 25, 30.
Seward, Frederick William, 4, 42.
Seward, William Henry, 4, 7-9, 13, 22 (mention).
Sewell, William Joyce, 52, 55.
Shafter, William Rufus, mentioned, 53, 55.
Sheridan, Philip Henry, 9, 10.
Sherman, William Tecumseh, 10, 22.
Silliman, Benjamin, 44.
Skilton, Julius A., 12, 14, 16, 23, 32.
Slavery - Cuba, 15, 18, 19, 57.
Sloan, Samuel, 30, 32, 34, 36.
Smith, Jaspar, 13-15.
Sonora, Mexico, 11, 40, 91, 92.
Soto, Mariano B., 23.
Southern Pacific Railroad, 60, 81, 82.
Spanish-American War, 1898, 53-55, 73.
Spofford, Ainsworth Rand, 43.
Spofford, Richard Smith, 43, 44, 46.
Springer, James H., 13.
Springer, Joseph A., 13, 16.
Steamers, 19, 36, 76.
Stevens, Simon, 21, 24, 25.
Stillman, James, 51.
Sturm, Herman, 7 (copy), 11.
Sullivan, James, 19.
Sumner, Charles, 9, 26 (mention).
Swank, James Moore, 28, 31.
Taylor, Moses, 13, 41.
Taylor, R. W., 13, 17.
Texas - Mexico border, 23, 33, 34, 43, 59.
Texas railroads, 19-21, 23-26, 29, 30, 32-36, 39, 40, 57, 61, 83, 84.
Thomson, J. Edgar, 4, 9.
Thornton, Sir Edward, 38.
Treaties, 5, 57, 58, 69.
Tronbridge, J. T., 22.
Uhink, Julio F., 11, 20.
Uhink, Valentin, 12.
Union and Central Pacific Railroad - Consolidation, 79.
U. S. Centennial Exposition, 34-36.
Vega, Placido, mentioned, 7, 11,
Velasco, Emilio, 20.
Venezuelan boundary, 48-51.
Vennon, Henry G., 44.
Vera Cruz Railroad, 1, 2, 22, 85.
Vernon, E. G., 45.
Ward, Elijah, 18, 19.
Ward, Samuel, 9, 45.
Washington Territory, 42.
Washington Treaty, 1871, 19.
Welles, Gideon, 4 (copy).
Wells, David Ames, 22.
West, Joseph Rodman, 10, 19.
Wetmore, Charles A., 43.
White, Andrew Dickson, 26, 49, 50.
Whiting, William, 19.
Whitney, Josiah Dwight, 2.
Whitney, William Dwight, 13.
Wilcox, Gurdon H., 44.
Wilkes, George, 9.
Wilson, George, 41.
Witherspoon, J. M., 10.
Worrall, [F. W.], 23.
Worrall, T. H., 11.
Wyman, John H., 23.
Yardley, E. T., 33.
Young, Edward, 34.
Zamacona, Manuel, 19, 21-23, 32, 39.
Zola trial, 52.